[{"question": "  what\u0092s so funny?", "answer": " oh, nothing, no. it\u0092s an acting exercise, i\u0092m practising my fake laugh.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 1, "asentId": 2}, {"question": "  oh, no-no, no-no-no, there\u0092s none of that in here.", "answer": " oh come on man! at least let me finish this last one.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 7, "asentId": 8}, {"question": " okay, but only if you give me a drag.", "answer": " okay.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 9, "asentId": 10}, {"question": " okay, that\u0092s like the least fun game ever.", "answer": " well, i\u0092m really sick of your smoking, so i brought something that is going to help you quit.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 15, "asentId": 16}, {"question": " come on, it\u0092s a hypnosis tape. this woman at work used it for two weeks straight and she hasn\u0092t smoked since.", "answer": " pffhah.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 19, "asentId": 20}, {"question": "  what\u0092s your problem?", "answer": " nothing, it\u0092s just that hypnosis is beyond crap.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 21, "asentId": 22}, {"question": " ross, i watched you get hypnotised in atlantic city.", "answer": " hey, that guy did not hypnotise me! okay.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 23, "asentId": 24}, {"question": " oh right, \u0091cause you always pull your pants down at the count of three and play wipe-out on your butt cheeks.", "answer": " all right, y'know forget hypnosis. the way to quit smoking is you have to dance naked in a field of heather, and then bath in the sweat of six healthy young men.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 25, "asentId": 26}, {"question": " here you go.", "answer": " oh, y'know what, i didn\u0092t want cinnamon on this.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 29, "asentId": 30}, {"question": "  hi!", "answer": " oh my god!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 33, "asentId": 34}, {"question": " hi!", "answer": " frank! hi!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 35, "asentId": 36}, {"question": " how are you?", "answer": " what are you doing here?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 37, "asentId": 38}, {"question": " oh, well y'know, i would\u0092ve called but i lost your phone number and then ah, my mom locked me out of the house so i couldn\u0092t find it. and then, i tried to find a pay phone, and ah, the receiver was cut off. so...", "answer": " what happened?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 39, "asentId": 40}, {"question": " ah, oh, the ah, vandalism.", "answer": " but, also, what happened between you and your mom?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 41, "asentId": 42}, {"question": " well, we got into a fight \u0091cause ah, she said i was to immature to get married.", "answer": " your getting married?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 43, "asentId": 44}, {"question": " oh, yeah!", "answer": " wow!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 45, "asentId": 46}, {"question": " my little brother\u0092s getting married!!", "answer": " oh, i knew you\u0092d be so cool about this. all right, ah, hey, do you want to meet her?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 47, "asentId": 48}, {"question": " do i?", "answer": " do you?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 49, "asentId": 50}, {"question": " yeah, i do, yeah.", "answer": " okay, cool, all right, she just ah, parking the truck.  i\u0092m gonna, i\u0092m gonna get my ah, my fianc\u008fe man!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 51, "asentId": 52}, {"question": " y'know, i would\u0092ve bet good money that he\u0092d be the first one of us to get married.", "answer": " yeah, isn\u0092t it fantastic?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 53, "asentId": 54}, {"question": " yeah, ah, but pheebs don\u0092t you think he\u0092s a little young to get married?", "answer": " what, he\u0092s 18.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 55, "asentId": 56}, {"question": " exactly, it\u0092ll be illegal for him to drink at his own bachelor party.", "answer": " yeah, or-or to get a hooker.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 57, "asentId": 58}, {"question": " always illegal joe.", "answer": "  hey! hey! this is ah, my fianc\u008fe, mrs. knight.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 59, "asentId": 60}, {"question": " y'know it-it\u0092s funny, um, frank told me so much about you, but your not how i pictured you at all.", "answer": " yeah, i\u0092m a big surprise.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 61, "asentId": 62}, {"question": " so, um, how-how did you guys meet?", "answer": " well um, i was in ah mrs. knight\u0092s ah, i mean alice, sorry, alice, i always do that. i was in her ah, home ec class.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 63, "asentId": 64}, {"question": " and he was my best student.", "answer": " yeah, she was my best teacher.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 65, "asentId": 66}, {"question": " if that doesn\u0092t keep kids in school, what will?", "answer": " and so now you guys are gonna be married?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 69, "asentId": 70}, {"question": " oh my god!! great!", "answer": " wow, kids. frank, are you sure you\u0092re ready for that?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 73, "asentId": 74}, {"question": " i mean, how hard can it be? y'know, i mean, y'know, babies, y'know who doesn\u0092t want babies right? and besides y'know, i never had a dad around, and ah, now-now i always will, \u0091cause y'know, it\u0092ll be me. right?", "answer": " y'know, i mean, really we do realise that there\u0092s an age difference between us.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 75, "asentId": 76}, {"question": " oh good! okay. \u0091cause you were acting like you didn\u0092t.", "answer": " oh no, but when it comes to love, what does age matter?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 77, "asentId": 78}, {"question": " and y'know what, i just realised, in the last year i\u0092ve only gone out with two guys, richard and julio. you gotta help me out here, you gotta set me up, you gotta get me back in the game.", "answer": " well, that shouldn\u0092t be a problem. i mean i work in fashion and all i meet are eligible straight men.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 81, "asentId": 82}, {"question": "  pete, can i get you something else?", "answer": " yeah, a slice of cheesecake and-and a date if you\u0092re given\u0092 \u0091em out.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 83, "asentId": 84}, {"question": " haven\u0092t you and i covered that topic?", "answer": " hmm, come on, you just said to her that you\u009a.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 85, "asentId": 86}, {"question": " aww, the only reason you want to go out with me because my blond wig, and the big boobs, and the fact that i serve you food.", "answer": " well, if that were true, i\u0092d dating my aunt ruth. and the two times we went out were just plain awkward.  come on, you think she should go out with me, don\u0092t you?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 87, "asentId": 88}, {"question": "  well, i mean, are you sure you want to go out with her? i mean that ain\u0092t a pretty picture in the morning, y\u0092know what i mean. that wig all in disarray, and boobs flung over the night stand, y'know.", "answer": " i mean really, think about it.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 89, "asentId": 90}, {"question": " no, i know, i know, that this is frank\u0092s life,  y'know. y'know, i don\u0092t want to be all judgmental, y'know, but this is sick, it\u0092s sick and wrong!", "answer": " pheebs, what, is it the age thing?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 93, "asentId": 94}, {"question": " no-no, oh, i\u0092m fine with the age thing y'know, until it starts sticking it\u0092s tongue down my little brother\u0092s throat!", "answer": " pheebs, he seems to enjoy it.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 95, "asentId": 96}, {"question": " but, i mean, do you think he\u0092s gonna enjoy it when he\u0092s up to his elbows in the diapers from all the babies they have to have right away?! this is not fair to frank,  and it-it\u0092s not fair to the babies, and y'know what, it\u0092s not good home economics.", "answer": " well, have-have you told him how you feel?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 97, "asentId": 98}, {"question": " yes. not out loud.", "answer": " pheebs, if you don\u0092t tell him, soon he\u0092s gonna be married, and then you\u0092re gonna hate yourself.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 99, "asentId": 100}, {"question": " come on, you guys, you have nothing to lose, i have everything to lose. do you want me to lose everything? everything?! ross and joey: no.", "answer": " okay, i\u0092m gonna go get frank.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 103, "asentId": 104}, {"question": " i think you should definitely go out with this guy.", "answer": " nah, he doesn\u0092t do anything for me.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 107, "asentId": 108}, {"question": " monica, last saturday night, what happened on walker: texas ranger?", "answer": " well, umm, walker was looking for this big bus load of kids\u009a.  all right, i get your point.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 109, "asentId": 110}, {"question": " all right.", "answer": "  hi.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 111, "asentId": 112}, {"question": " hey.", "answer": " y'know, i forgot the combination to this about a year ago? i just carry it around. do you have any chap stick?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 113, "asentId": 114}, {"question": " uh, yeah.", "answer": " hey, how are those tapes working out for ya?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 115, "asentId": 116}, {"question": " y'know what, pretty good.", "answer": " yeah?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 117, "asentId": 118}, {"question": " good! i haven\u0092t smoked yet today, i feel great, and-and-and confident, that is a stunning blouse.", "answer": " thank you.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 119, "asentId": 120}, {"question": " here you go.", "answer": " thanks", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 121, "asentId": 122}, {"question": " hey mon, let\u0092s give pete a chance come on, he was funny, he seems really nice, and that check thing was adorable.", "answer": " what check thing?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 123, "asentId": 124}, {"question": " as a joke, this customer at work who has a crush on me gave me a $20,000 tip. his number is on the check, he just did so i\u0092d call him.", "answer": "  pete becker. pete\u009a   is this him?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 125, "asentId": 126}, {"question": " that\u0092s bill clinton.", "answer": " who\u0092s he huggin\u0092?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 127, "asentId": 128}, {"question": " oh my god! that\u0092s pete! but why is bill huggin\u0092 pete?", "answer": " this guy invented moss 865! every office in the world uses that program!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 129, "asentId": 130}, {"question": " we use it!!", "answer": " there you go!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 131, "asentId": 132}, {"question": " oh my god, monica\u0092s gonna go out with a millionaire.", "answer": " i\u0092m not gonna go out with him.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 133, "asentId": 134}, {"question": " oh my god, i can\u0092t believe this is a real $20,000 check, oh this is just so exciting.", "answer": " or incredibly offensive.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 135, "asentId": 136}, {"question": " all we\u0092re saying is don\u0092t rush into anything.", "answer": " yeah, come on, think about it. you\u0092re 18, okay, she\u0092s 44, when you\u0092re 36, she\u0092s gonna be 88.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 141, "asentId": 142}, {"question": " what, you don\u0092t think i know that?", "answer": " look, the point is, there\u0092s a lot of women out there you haven\u0092t even had sex with yet!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 143, "asentId": 144}, {"question": " yeah, he-he\u0092s right, he\u0092s right. this is your time y'know, yeah, you\u0092re young, you\u0092re-you\u0092re weird, chicks dig that.", "answer": " okay, but isn\u0092t sex better when it\u0092s with one person that you really, really care about.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 145, "asentId": 146}, {"question": " yeah, in a poem maybe.", "answer": " no the man\u0092s right, that\u0092s what i had with rachel.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 147, "asentId": 148}, {"question": " you don\u0092t have it anymore?", "answer": " no, i ah, i slept with someone else.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 149, "asentId": 150}, {"question": " okay, so wait, all right, so how does that make things better?", "answer": " it didn\u0092t.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 151, "asentId": 152}, {"question": " okay, so what you used to have with rachel, is what i\u0092ve got with alice.", "answer": " now, wh-what, what is that like?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 153, "asentId": 154}, {"question": " it\u0092s so cool man, it\u0092s so, it\u0092s just \u0091cause being with her is so much better than like not being with her.", "answer": " yeah, yeah.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 155, "asentId": 156}, {"question": "  why can\u0092t i find that?", "answer": " don\u0092t ask me, i had it and i blew it!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 157, "asentId": 158}, {"question": " well, i want it!", "answer": " you can have it!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 159, "asentId": 160}, {"question": " i don\u0092t know, maybe i can\u0092t. i mean, maybe there\u0092s something wrong with me.", "answer": " oh, no! no!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 161, "asentId": 162}, {"question": " it\u0092s out there man! i\u0092ve seen it! i got it!!", "answer": " then you hold on to it!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 163, "asentId": 164}, {"question": " all right, man!!", "answer": " all right, congratulations you lucky bastard!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 165, "asentId": 166}, {"question": "  you\u0092re frank\u0092s best man?!", "answer": " i couldn\u0092t help it, there love is so pure.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 167, "asentId": 168}, {"question": " well then,  what about you?! huh?!", "answer": " i\u0092m the ring bearer.  commercial break", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 169, "asentId": 170}, {"question": " oh my god, who died on this?!", "answer": " yeah, i know. it\u0092s a real mustard-tastrophe. can you help me?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 173, "asentId": 174}, {"question": " absolutely. okay, first we\u0092ll start with a little club soda and salt, and then if that doesn\u0092t work we can go back to\u009a", "answer": " y'know what, forget it. it\u0092s ruined.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 175, "asentId": 176}, {"question": " oh no-no, never say that. if we can\u0092t get it out then we can cut around the stain, add a little lace, you make a stylish throw.", "answer": " or instead, maybe you could just not marry my brother frank.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 177, "asentId": 178}, {"question": " okay, that\u0092s great, but can we make it smaller? can we make it fit on the head of a pin? i love when we make things fit on the head of a pin.", "answer": " got it. yeah all right. yeah, okay.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 179, "asentId": 180}, {"question": " you have a miss monica geller here.", "answer": " uh, absolutely, yeah, send her in.  hi.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 181, "asentId": 182}, {"question": " hang on a second.  i\u0092ll-i\u0092ll talk to you in the morning.  i\u0092m sorry what?", "answer": " seriously, what is this supposed to mean?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 185, "asentId": 186}, {"question": " well, y\u0092know, i never know how much to tip.", "answer": " you\u0092re supposed to double the tax. not double the tax of romania. i mean, what\u0092s-what\u0092s the deal? are you, are you trying to buy me? is this the way you get girls to go out with you?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 187, "asentId": 188}, {"question": " umm, i\u0092m still here.", "answer": "  you\u0092re taking this all wrong. because, if i didn\u0092t leave you that tip, you wouldn\u0092t of come down here, we wouldn\u0092t be having this argument, and there wouldn\u0092t be this ah, heat between us.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 189, "asentId": 190}, {"question": " what?!", "answer": " come on, you gotta admit that our relationship is ah, is hitting a new level now. \u0091cause you used to be like the chef, and i was the customer, and now we\u0092re like this-this couple that fights.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 191, "asentId": 192}, {"question": " okay, umm, you\u0092re a loon.", "answer": " look, forget the check, okay.  i like you. i think you\u0092re great. come on, what do you say?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 193, "asentId": 194}, {"question": " i don\u0092t know.", "answer": " why not?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 195, "asentId": 196}, {"question": " \u0091cause i don\u0092t want to encourage this kind of behaviour.", "answer": " one meal! that\u0092s all i\u0092m asking for. please? we go out, we eat, and if you don\u0092t have a good time, i give you ten grand, we call it even.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 197, "asentId": 198}, {"question": "  hi.  wait, no! just put the mail down. it\u0092s-it\u0092s me!", "answer": " okay. whoa, sorry. why were you just like all in the dark?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 199, "asentId": 200}, {"question": " oh well, um, your, your laundry just smelled so good, that i thought i\u0092d curl up in it. is that all right?", "answer": " oh, yeah, sure. so, how was your day?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 201, "asentId": 202}, {"question": " oh, well just probably the worst one since i\u0092ve been alive.", "answer": " what umm, what happened?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 203, "asentId": 204}, {"question": " umm, alice ah, she ah, called it off.", "answer": " oh no. did umm, did she say why?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 205, "asentId": 206}, {"question": " uh, no, not really, just that i was too young, y'know, but i don\u0092t see how i could all of the sudden be too young, \u0091cause i\u0092m older than i was when we first got together.", "answer": " yeah, yeah, no, i don\u0092t, i don\u0092t know. but, y'know what, maybe it\u0092s just all for the best?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 207, "asentId": 208}, {"question": " yeah, if the best is like unbelievable pain!", "answer": " oh, sweetie, oh.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 209, "asentId": 210}, {"question": " y'know, i just was finally happy y'know. for the first time in my life! after my dad left me, and then, and then getting arrested for stealing those birds, and then, and then the whole punctured lung thing! i can, it\u0092s still really hard to take deep breaths in cold weather, but with alice all that stuff kinda went away. and now it\u0092s, and now it\u0092s gone and i don\u0092t know why!", "answer": " uh, well i can tell you why. it\u0092s, it\u0092s because of me. but, y'know what, i only did it because i love you. okay?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 211, "asentId": 212}, {"question": " what?", "answer": " umm, well i, i kinda had a little chat with alice, and i sort of made her see why you two shouldn\u0092t be together, y'know. and you\u0092re gonna see it to, one day, you really, really will.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 213, "asentId": 214}, {"question": " wait a minute, wait, this is because of you?", "answer": " okay.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 215, "asentId": 216}, {"question": " well, you, wait no, my mother didn\u0092t want us to be together, but the worst thing she ever did was tie me to the porch.", "answer": " okay, but.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 217, "asentId": 218}, {"question": " oh my god! the millionaire\u0092s here!", "answer": "  oh my god!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 221, "asentId": 222}, {"question": " guys, please, i\u0092m just gonna have dinner with him. okay?", "answer": " okay, okay, just because he buys you dinner, does not mean you owe him anything.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 223, "asentId": 224}, {"question": " i know!!", "answer": " okay, then get the lobster!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 225, "asentId": 226}, {"question": "   hey!", "answer": " hi.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 227, "asentId": 228}, {"question": " hi!!", "answer": " hey!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 229, "asentId": 230}, {"question": " hey, how much cash do you got in your pocket right now?", "answer": " and that\u0092s why, i\u0092m not inviting you in for a drink.  bye.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 233, "asentId": 234}, {"question": " oh-no-no-no-no\u009a.", "answer": " just one drink?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 235, "asentId": 236}, {"question": "  so, where do you want to go?", "answer": " hey, you like pizza?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 237, "asentId": 238}, {"question": " oh, that\u0092s sounds great.", "answer": " i know a great little place.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 239, "asentId": 240}, {"question": " you\u0092re, hey, you\u0092re not paying for the pizza!", "answer": " oh come on, it\u0092s only fair, you paid for the flight. now is, is that enough lire?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 241, "asentId": 242}, {"question": " ahh, i\u0092d throw another thousand on that.", "answer": " why, how much is that?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 243, "asentId": 244}, {"question": " hey, frank. look, okay, i know that you think i did like this totally evil thing, but i so didn\u0092t. there\u0092s someone here who can explain this better than i can.", "answer": " hi frank.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 251, "asentId": 252}, {"question": " hi, mrs. knight.", "answer": " phoebe\u0092s right frank. i know it\u0092s hard to hear, but it would\u0092ve been wrong to go through with it. i-i-i was being selfish, even though we, we want the same things now, in the future we may not.  is that it, is that what it is?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 253, "asentId": 254}, {"question": " yeah, but not just that.", "answer": " right, not just that. umm, even though we love each other as much as we do, none the less\u009a", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 255, "asentId": 256}, {"question": " none the less.", "answer": " none the less. umm, you\u0092re too young to, to really know what you want.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 257, "asentId": 258}, {"question": " cigarette\u0092s don\u0092t control you. you are a strong, confident woman, who does not need to smoke.", "answer": "  joey\u0092s your best friend. you want to make him a cheese sandwich everyday.  and you also want to buy him hundreds of dollars worth of pants.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 261, "asentId": 262}]